그
그를 잊지 못해서 아파하나요
Geureul ijji mothaesuh apahanayo
くるる いっち もてそ あぱはなよ
It hurts since I can't forget that
彼を忘れられなくて苦しんでるの？
그
그대가 있을 자리가 여긴 아닌가요
Geudaega isseul jariga yuhgin aningayo
くでが いっする ちゃりが よぎ なにんがよ
Look like here is not the place Where you're supposed to be
君がいる場所はここじゃないの？
나를 위한 거라면 참을 필욘 없죠
Nareul wihan guhramyuhn chameul piryo uhbjyo
なるる うぃはん ごらみょん ちゃむる ぴりょん おっちょ
You don't have to hold back for me . . .
僕の為なら我慢する必要はないよ
언젠간 끝나버릴 테니
Uhnjengan kkeutnabuhrilteni
おんじぇんがん っくんなぼりる てに
It all will end someday too anyway
いつかは終わってしまうから
내 사랑이 제자리로 오지 못하고
Nae sarangi jejariro oji mothago
ね さらぎ ちぇじゃりろ おじ もたご
My love just can't seem to reach you
僕の愛が 元の場所に帰ることができず
흘린 눈물만큼 멀리 가네요
Heullin noonmool mankeum muhlli ganeyo
ふりん ぬんむるまんくん もり がねよ
Just as much as the amount of tears that flowed,
It's still far away to go
流した涙の分だけ遠ざかって行くよ
나는 잊어야 하죠 그대 너무 그리워
Naneun ijuhyahajyo geudae nuhmoo geuriwuh
なぬん いじょや はじょ くで のむ くりうぉ
I have to forget you though I miss you so much . . .
僕は忘れなきゃいけないね 君がとても恋しいよ
나를 아프게 할지는 몰라도 잊어요
Nareul apeuge haljineun mollado ijuhyo
なるる あぷげ はるじぬん もらど いじょよ
Even if you never know how much it hurts, I will forget . . .
僕を苦しめるかも知れなくても忘れるよ